channelpear.com 2018-05-26

# channel PEAR - Privacy Policy

Your use of channelpear.com ("the Website") and any services provided by Jidly LLC., a Delaware Limited Liability Company, (hereinafter "we", "us", "our", "channelpear.com", "channelPEAR", "channel PEAR", "channel pear") is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service . Such services and the Website are collectively referred to in this Privacy Policy as the "Services." We are pleased to provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our practices with respect to how we collect and use personally identifiable information and other information in connection with your access to the Website and use of the Services. WHEN YOU ACCESS THE WEBSITE AND/OR UTILIZE THE SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, OR TO ANY CHANGES WE MAY SUBSEQUENTLY MAKE, IMMEDIATELY STOP ACCESSING THE WEBSITE AND/OR UTILIZING THE SERVICES. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to the management of your personal information by channel PEAR as described herein and as provided in the Terms of Service.

##### Information We Collect

The types of information that we collect fall under two general categories: personally identifiable information ("PII") and non-personally identifiable information ("Non-PII"). PII consists of any information that can be used to specifically identify you as an individual, whereas Non-PII consists of aggregate information or any information that does not reveal your identity.

The data that we might regularly collect about visitors to the Website (e.g., IP address, browser type, pages accessed, duration of visit, etc.) does not enable us to personally identify you, and that is not our intention. We do collect PII, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and credit card information, when you voluntarily provide it in connection with your registration for a channel PEAR account and/or your subscribing to a channel PEAR premium service.

##### Use of Information

If and when you elect to submit registration to receive an account, channel PEAR will use your PII and Non-PII primarily to provide you with the Services. The information may also be used to verify your authority to access the Services and/or to contact you when reasonably necessary. channel PEAR may also use any information you have provided as reasonably necessary to administer or provide customer support for the Services, and to provide you with periodic e-mail communications about your account. In addition to the information that you submit in connection with your registration to receive an account, channel PEAR may collect information about you in the following ways:

##### Log Files

Any time you visit the Website, our servers have the ability to automatically gather information from your browser such as your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp and number of clicks. We may use this information to analyze trends, administer the Website, prevent fraud, track visitor movement in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information. For example, we may log your IP address for system administration purposes or to track use of the Website and the Services. This gives us information on which parts of the Website users are visiting. We do not share the log files externally unless otherwise specified.

##### Cookies

We might use "cookies" to keep track of some types of information while you are visiting the Website or using the Services. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record keeping purposes. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate the Website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time.

Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your on-line activity on the Website, such as the pages you visit, the links you click and the searches you conduct on the Website. If you create and sign into an account on the Website, we may record your user or member ID and the name associated with your user or member ID in the cookie file on your computer. We also may record your password in this cookie file if you indicated that you would like your password saved for automatic sign-in. In the case of sites and services that do not use a user or member ID, the cookie will contain a unique identifier. We may allow our authorized service providers to serve cookies from the Website to allow them to assist us in various activities, such as doing analysis and research on the effectiveness of the Website, content and advertising.

You may delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings (typically by clicking "Tools" or "Help" in the toolbar of your browser.) If you do so, some of the features of the Services may not function properly.

We may allow third parties, including our affiliated companies, advertising companies and advertising networks, to display advertisements on the Website. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. The Website does not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third party's privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness.

Web Beacons. Web beacons (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags or web bugs) are small graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, which are used to track the on-line movements of Internet users or to access cookies. Unlike cookies, which are stored on the user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded "invisibly" on the web pages (or in e-mail) and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

We may use web beacons to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited certain pages and to understand usage patterns. We also may include web beacons in promotional (or other) e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. We also may receive an anonymous identification number if you come to the Website from an on-line advertisement displayed on a third party website.

##### E-mails

We require an e-mail address from you when you submit registration to receive an account. We may use your e-mail for both transactional purposes (e.g., order confirmation, billing, renewal processing, match notifications, etc.) and promotional purposes (e.g., newsletters, new product offerings, special discounts, event notifications, special third party offers, etc.). E-mail messages we send to you may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the e-mails, including whether the e-mail was opened and what links (if any) were clicked. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Services, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. We fully comply with the requirements of the U.S. CAN-SPAM Act of 2003.

##### Demographic Data

Demographic data may also be collected by us from the Website. We may use this data to customize our users' experience, showing users content in which we think they might be interested, and displaying the content according to user preferences. Some of this information may be shared with advertisers on a non-personally identifiable basis.

##### Use for Research

In addition to the uses outlined above, by using the Website you agree to allow us to anonymously use the information from you and your experiences to research ways to improve the Services and the user experience that we offer.

##### Disclosure

channel PEAR will not disclose your personal information to third parties for any reason whatsoever unless channel PEAR believes it is reasonably necessary to comply with law, regulation or other governmental authority or to prevent harm to you or others. channel PEAR may also contract with various third parties who help us provide and maintain the Services. Finally, channel PEAR may disclose your PII upon a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of channel PEAR's stock or assets or upon any bankruptcy or other corporate reorganization.

##### Links

For your convenience, we may provide links to certain third party websites or referrals to certain third parties' products or services. If you choose to visit a third party's website or use its products or services, please be aware that such third party's privacy policy, and not this Privacy Policy, will govern your activities and any information you disclose while interacting with such third party.

##### Collection of Information from Children

We do not knowingly collect PII relating to children or target the Website or the Services to children. In the event that we learn that we have collected PII from anyone under 13 years of age without prior parental consent, we will take steps to promptly delete such information in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. By providing your PII to channel PEAR through the Website, you represent that you are 18 years of age or older.

##### Policy Changes

channel PEAR reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy without prior notice. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued visits to the Website and/or use of the Services will be subject to channel PEAR's then-current privacy policy.

##### No Error-Free Performance

channel PEAR does not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. Accordingly, we welcome your feedback regarding any privacy concerns that you may have, including how we can improve this Privacy Policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with it.

##### Legal Notices

This Privacy Policy is expressly subject to the terms in our Terms of Service, including terms regarding limitations on damages, disclaimers of warranties and resolution of disputes. Our Terms of Service take precedence over any conflicting provision in this Privacy Policy.

##### Questions

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at:

ATTN: Channel PEAR Jidly, LLC  
1521 CONCORD PIKE STE 301  
WILMINGTON, DE 19803  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

##### Choice/Opt-Out

You may use the following options for removing your information from our e-mail database if you wish to opt out of receiving promotional e-mails and newsletters: • Click on the "unsubscribe" link on the bottom of the e-mail; • For any services that allow you to control which e-mails you receive, go to the e-mail settings page from your account home page and un-check the undesired promotions.

##### Updating Your Information

channel PEAR provides users with the following options for changing and modifying information previously submitted: • Send us an e-mail at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we will be happy to assist you. • For any services where you have an account page, you may change your billing information (if applicable), e-mail address, password and other information from the account settings or preferences page.

##### Acceptance of Privacy Policy

Your access to and use of the Website and the Services, including any dispute concerning privacy, is expressly subject to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. BY ACCESSING THE WEBSITE AND/OR USING THE SERVICES, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THE APPLICABLE TERMS OF SERVICE.
